{"id":"mem-0001","text":"Good morning Jarvis! What's on the calendar today? I feel like it's going to be a busy Thursday.","title":"Morning Greeting","synapticTags":["morning-routine","greeting","calendar"],"valence":15,"importance":0.3,"arousal":20,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-early-morning","timestampMs":1749128400000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.2,"challenge":0.0,"urgency":0.1}
{"id":"mem-0002","text":"Good morning Mike! Today is Thursday, June 5th. Here's your rundown: 10 AM CareConnect stakeholder review with Greg and the engineering leads, Ethan has soccer practice at 4 PM at the Frisco FC fields, and Sarah mentioned she needs you to pick up Lily from Little Stars by 5:30 since she has a client call.","title":"Jarvis Morning Briefing","synapticTags":["morning-routine","calendar","careconnect","soccer","daycare"],"valence":10,"importance":0.4,"arousal":15,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-early-morning","timestampMs":1749128430000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"CareConnect","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Greg Holloway","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Ethan Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Frisco FC","type":"ORGANIZATION"},{"name":"Sarah Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Lily Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Little Stars Daycare","type":"ORGANIZATION"}],"memoryType":"SEMANTIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.2,"challenge":0.1,"urgency":0.3}
{"id":"mem-0003","text":"Jarvis, I need to prep for the CareConnect stakeholder review at 10. Greg's been pushing back on the patient messaging feature — he wants to cut it from the MVP to save two sprints. I think it's critical for user adoption. Can you pull up the user research data Anika compiled last week?","title":"CareConnect Demo Prep","synapticTags":["careconnect","work","stakeholder-review","greg-conflict","feature-priority","anika"],"valence":-20,"importance":1.8,"arousal":75,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-morning","timestampMs":1749135600000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"CareConnect","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Greg Holloway","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Anika Patel","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Vertex Health","type":"ORGANIZATION"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.8,"challenge":0.6,"urgency":0.9}
{"id":"mem-0004","text":"I've pulled up Anika's user research summary from May 28th. Key finding: 73% of beta users listed in-app messaging as their #1 requested feature. The competitive analysis also shows that MyChart and Athena both launched messaging in their last release cycle. I can format this into talking points for the meeting if you'd like.","title":"User Research Data for CareConnect","synapticTags":["careconnect","work","anika","feature-priority","stakeholder-review"],"valence":20,"importance":1.5,"arousal":45,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-morning","timestampMs":1749135630000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Anika Patel","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"CareConnect","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Vertex Health","type":"ORGANIZATION"}],"memoryType":"SEMANTIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.7,"challenge":0.3,"urgency":0.8}
{"id":"mem-0005","text":"Yes, format those into talking points. Also add the churn risk data — if we don't have messaging, we'll lose the Baylor Scott partnership. That's a $2M ARR account. Greg needs to see the revenue impact, not just the engineering effort.","title":"Stakeholder Talking Points Strategy","synapticTags":["careconnect","work","stakeholder-review","greg-conflict","roadmap"],"valence":-10,"importance":2.2,"arousal":85,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-morning","timestampMs":1749135900000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Greg Holloway","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"CareConnect","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Vertex Health","type":"ORGANIZATION"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.9,"challenge":0.7,"urgency":1.0}
{"id":"mem-0006","text":"Done. I've prepared a one-page brief with three sections: User Demand (73% request rate), Competitive Pressure (MyChart, Athena), and Revenue Risk ($2M Baylor Scott ARR). Want me to also draft a compromise proposal — like a phased rollout where messaging ships in v1.1 instead of being cut entirely?","title":"Jarvis Stakeholder Brief","synapticTags":["careconnect","work","stakeholder-review","roadmap"],"valence":25,"importance":1.6,"arousal":40,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-morning","timestampMs":1749135930000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"CareConnect","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Vertex Health","type":"ORGANIZATION"}],"memoryType":"SEMANTIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.7,"challenge":0.4,"urgency":0.8}
{"id":"mem-0007","text":"That's actually brilliant — yes, draft the phased approach. If we frame it as 'messaging in v1.1 with a beta cohort at Baylor', Greg can't argue the engineering scope is too big for MVP. Good thinking Jarvis.","title":"Phased Messaging Compromise","synapticTags":["careconnect","work","stakeholder-review","greg-conflict","roadmap"],"valence":35,"importance":1.9,"arousal":60,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-morning","timestampMs":1749136200000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Greg Holloway","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"CareConnect","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.9,"challenge":0.5,"urgency":0.9}
{"id":"mem-0008","text":"Jarvis, quick question — did Sarah say what time Lily's swim lesson is on Saturday? I want to make sure it doesn't conflict with Ethan's soccer game.","title":"Weekend Schedule Check","synapticTags":["swim-lessons","soccer","calendar","parenting"],"valence":5,"importance":0.5,"arousal":25,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-midday","timestampMs":1749146400000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Sarah Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Lily Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Ethan Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.5,"challenge":0.1,"urgency":0.3}
{"id":"mem-0009","text":"Lily's swim lesson at the Frisco Aquatic Center is at 9:30 AM on Saturday. Ethan's Frisco FC game is at 2 PM at the Toyota Soccer Center. No conflict — you'll have plenty of time between them. Want me to add both to the shared family calendar?","title":"Weekend Activity Schedule","synapticTags":["swim-lessons","soccer","frisco-fc","calendar"],"valence":15,"importance":0.5,"arousal":15,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-midday","timestampMs":1749146430000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Lily Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Frisco Aquatic Center","type":"LOCATION"},{"name":"Ethan Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Frisco FC","type":"ORGANIZATION"}],"memoryType":"SEMANTIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.4,"challenge":0.0,"urgency":0.2}
{"id":"mem-0010","text":"Jarvis, remind me to call the mortgage broker tomorrow morning. I saw that 30-year fixed rates dropped to 5.8% and I want to ask about our refinance options. We're paying 6.5% right now which is insane.","title":"Mortgage Refinance Reminder","synapticTags":["mortgage","refinance","finance","reminder"],"valence":-15,"importance":1.4,"arousal":55,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-midday","timestampMs":1749148200000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.6,"challenge":0.4,"urgency":0.5}
{"id":"mem-0011","text":"Reminder set for tomorrow at 8:30 AM: Call mortgage broker about refinancing. Quick math on the savings — at 5.8% vs your current 6.5% on a $420K balance, you'd save roughly $195/month or about $2,340 per year. Definitely worth exploring.","title":"Refinance Savings Estimate","synapticTags":["mortgage","refinance","finance","reminder"],"valence":20,"importance":1.2,"arousal":35,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-midday","timestampMs":1749148230000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"}],"memoryType":"SEMANTIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.6,"challenge":0.3,"urgency":0.4}
{"id":"mem-0012","text":"The stakeholder review went better than expected. I presented the phased approach for CareConnect messaging and Greg actually agreed to v1.1 with the Baylor beta. Anika did great presenting the user research — she's really growing as a PM. I think this is the first time I've walked out of a meeting with Greg feeling like we actually collaborated.","title":"CareConnect Review Success","synapticTags":["careconnect","work","stakeholder-review","greg-conflict","anika","mentoring"],"valence":60,"importance":2.5,"arousal":95,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-afternoon","timestampMs":1749157200000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"CareConnect","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Greg Holloway","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Anika Patel","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Vertex Health","type":"ORGANIZATION"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.9,"challenge":0.6,"urgency":0.7}
{"id":"mem-0013","text":"That's a great outcome Mike! It sounds like the data-driven approach with the phased compromise really worked. And it's wonderful to see Anika stepping up — would you like me to note this as a coaching milestone for her Q3 review?","title":"Jarvis Meeting Debrief","synapticTags":["careconnect","work","mentoring","anika"],"valence":30,"importance":1.3,"arousal":30,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-afternoon","timestampMs":1749157230000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Anika Patel","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"CareConnect","type":"SOFTWARE"}],"memoryType":"SEMANTIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.6,"challenge":0.2,"urgency":0.2}
{"id":"mem-0014","text":"Yes definitely note that for Anika's review. Hey also, I just picked up Lily from daycare and she was so happy today — apparently she painted a picture of our family including the dog we don't have yet. She keeps asking when we're getting a puppy. Sarah and I need to actually make a decision on this soon.","title":"Lily's Puppy Campaign","synapticTags":["parenting","lily-milestone","daycare"],"valence":55,"importance":1.1,"arousal":70,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-afternoon","timestampMs":1749160800000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Lily Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Sarah Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Little Stars Daycare","type":"ORGANIZATION"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.7,"challenge":0.3,"urgency":0.2}
{"id":"mem-0015","text":"That's adorable! The painted family dog — she's persistent. If you and Sarah do decide to move forward, I've been tracking a few golden retriever breeders in the DFW area and there are also some great rescues. The Frisco Humane Society had golden mixes available last time I checked. Want me to put together a comparison?","title":"Puppy Options Research","synapticTags":["parenting"],"valence":25,"importance":0.8,"arousal":25,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-afternoon","timestampMs":1749160830000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Lily Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Sarah Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Frisco","type":"LOCATION"}],"memoryType":"SEMANTIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.6,"challenge":0.2,"urgency":0.1}
{"id":"mem-0016","text":"Jarvis, what should we do for dinner tonight? Sarah's got a client call until 7 and I've got both kids. Something quick that Ethan and Lily will both eat — and no, Lily won't eat anything green right now.","title":"Dinner Planning","synapticTags":["meal-prep","dinner-plan","parenting","cooking"],"valence":-5,"importance":0.6,"arousal":40,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-evening","timestampMs":1749170400000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Sarah Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Ethan Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Lily Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.4,"challenge":0.2,"urgency":0.5}
{"id":"mem-0017","text":"How about sheet pan chicken quesadillas? 20 minutes, one pan, and you can cut Lily's into fun shapes. Ethan can add jalapeños to his if he wants. You've got tortillas, shredded cheese, and chicken breast in the fridge — I checked the grocery inventory this morning. Just dice the chicken, season with cumin and chili powder, and assemble.","title":"Quick Dinner Recipe","synapticTags":["meal-prep","recipe","dinner-plan","cooking"],"valence":20,"importance":0.5,"arousal":20,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-evening","timestampMs":1749170430000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Lily Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Ethan Thompson","type":"PERSON"}],"memoryType":"PROCEDURAL","recallCount":0,"interest":0.4,"challenge":0.1,"urgency":0.4}
{"id":"mem-0018","text":"Ethan's homework is done — he had a reading comprehension worksheet about the solar system. He got all the questions right except the one about Neptune's moons. He's reading at a 4th grade level already which is great for end of 3rd grade. Mrs. Patterson also texted that he did well at piano today and is ready to start a new piece next week.","title":"Ethan's Academic Update","synapticTags":["school","homework","reading","piano","ethan-growth"],"valence":50,"importance":1.0,"arousal":45,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-evening","timestampMs":1749174000000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Ethan Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Mrs. Patterson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Liberty Elementary","type":"ORGANIZATION"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.7,"challenge":0.2,"urgency":0.1}
{"id":"mem-0019","text":"Bedtime was rough. Lily had a full meltdown because her stuffed elephant wasn't in the right spot on her bed. Forty minutes of screaming. I know it's developmentally normal for a three-year-old but man, it really tests your patience. Sarah took over when she got off her call and somehow got Lily down in ten minutes. Mom magic.","title":"Lily Bedtime Meltdown","synapticTags":["parenting","bedtime","tantrum","lily-milestone","sibling-dynamics"],"valence":-40,"importance":1.3,"arousal":160,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-evening","timestampMs":1749178800000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Lily Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Sarah Thompson","type":"PERSON"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.6,"challenge":0.6,"urgency":0.7}
{"id":"mem-0020","text":"Jarvis, logging today's journal. Overall a good day despite the bedtime chaos. CareConnect meeting went really well — Greg agreed to the phased messaging approach which is huge. Anika is stepping up. Ethan crushed his homework and piano. Lily's still campaigning for a dog, and her bedtime tantrums are something else. Need to talk to Sarah this weekend about whether we're really ready for a puppy on top of everything. Also need to call the mortgage broker tomorrow — those rates dropping could save us real money. Feeling grateful but tired.","title":"Thursday Journal Entry","synapticTags":["evening-journal","reflection","careconnect","parenting","finance"],"valence":20,"importance":0.8,"arousal":25,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-evening","timestampMs":1749182400000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"CareConnect","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Greg Holloway","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Anika Patel","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Ethan Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Lily Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Sarah Thompson","type":"PERSON"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.3,"challenge":0.1,"urgency":0.0}
{"id":"mem-0021","text":"Great day overall Mike. I've logged your journal entry and updated the running notes. A few things for tomorrow: mortgage broker call at 8:30 AM, CareConnect sprint planning at 11 AM, and Ethan's soccer practice at 4 PM. Rest well — you've earned it.","title":"Jarvis Evening Summary","synapticTags":["evening-journal","calendar","reminder"],"valence":15,"importance":0.4,"arousal":10,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-05-evening","timestampMs":1749182430000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"CareConnect","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Ethan Thompson","type":"PERSON"}],"memoryType":"SEMANTIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.2,"challenge":0.0,"urgency":0.1}
