{"id":"mem-0022","text":"Good morning Jarvis. Wednesday already — week's flying by. Did the mortgage broker office confirm my callback for Friday?","title":"Morning Check-in","synapticTags":["morning-routine","greeting","mortgage","refinance"],"valence":5,"importance":0.3,"arousal":15,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-04-early-morning","timestampMs":1749042000000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.3,"challenge":0.0,"urgency":0.2}
{"id":"mem-0023","text":"Morning Mike! No callback confirmation yet from First United Mortgage — they typically respond within 24 hours. I'll ping you when it comes in. Today you're working from home. You have a 1:1 with Anika at 9:30 AM, sprint retro at 2 PM, and Ethan has piano with Mrs. Patterson at 4:30.","title":"Wednesday Morning Briefing","synapticTags":["morning-routine","calendar","mentoring","piano"],"valence":10,"importance":0.4,"arousal":15,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-04-early-morning","timestampMs":1749042030000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Anika Patel","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Ethan Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Mrs. Patterson","type":"PERSON"}],"memoryType":"SEMANTIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.2,"challenge":0.0,"urgency":0.2}
{"id":"mem-0024","text":"Jarvis, I'm prepping for my 1:1 with Anika. She's been handling the CareConnect user research really well but I want to push her to start owning the feature prioritization process. What coaching frameworks work well for junior PMs stepping into more ownership?","title":"Anika Coaching Prep","synapticTags":["mentoring","anika","work","careconnect"],"valence":20,"importance":1.2,"arousal":45,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-04-morning","timestampMs":1749045000000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Anika Patel","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"CareConnect","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.8,"challenge":0.5,"urgency":0.4}
{"id":"mem-0025","text":"Great instinct on pushing Anika toward ownership. A few frameworks that work well for junior PMs: 1) RACI model — explicitly assign her as 'Responsible' for a feature area. 2) The 'I do, we do, you do' scaffolding — have her lead the next prioritization meeting while you observe. 3) Decision journaling — ask her to document her reasoning so you can review together. Given her strong research skills, maybe start by letting her own the patient onboarding feature prioritization end-to-end?","title":"PM Coaching Frameworks","synapticTags":["mentoring","anika","work"],"valence":15,"importance":1.0,"arousal":30,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-04-morning","timestampMs":1749045030000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Anika Patel","type":"PERSON"}],"memoryType":"SEMANTIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.7,"challenge":0.4,"urgency":0.3}
{"id":"mem-0026","text":"Sarah just told me Patricia called — she's been having some knee pain and her doctor wants to do an MRI. It's probably nothing but Sarah's worried, especially after what happened with Robert. I told her Patricia is tough and this is just normal aging stuff, but I can tell she's anxious.","title":"Patricia Health Concern","synapticTags":["patricia","family-visit","health","robert-memory"],"valence":-35,"importance":2.0,"arousal":90,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-04-morning","timestampMs":1749049200000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Sarah Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Patricia Morales","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Robert Morales","type":"PERSON"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.7,"challenge":0.4,"urgency":0.5}
{"id":"mem-0027","text":"I'm sorry to hear about Patricia's knee. It's understandable that Sarah would be anxious given what happened with Robert. Knee MRIs are very routine — most commonly it's a meniscus tear or arthritis, both very manageable. Would it help if I looked up orthopedic specialists in the Austin area in case she needs a referral? Or maybe you could suggest Sarah call Patricia tonight for a longer chat?","title":"Patricia Health Support","synapticTags":["patricia","health","family-visit","austin"],"valence":5,"importance":1.2,"arousal":30,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-04-morning","timestampMs":1749049230000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Patricia Morales","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Sarah Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Robert Morales","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Austin","type":"LOCATION"}],"memoryType":"SEMANTIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.6,"challenge":0.3,"urgency":0.4}
{"id":"mem-0028","text":"Yeah, look up some ortho specialists in Austin. And good call on the longer chat — I'll suggest that to Sarah. Switching gears — I need to figure out what to get Dave for his birthday. The Nguyens are having us over for a BBQ this Saturday. He's into smoking meats, so maybe some kind of grilling accessory?","title":"Dave's Birthday Gift","synapticTags":["neighbors","nguyen-family","birthday-gift","shopping","bbq"],"valence":15,"importance":0.6,"arousal":30,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-04-midday","timestampMs":1749056400000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Dave Nguyen","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Kim Nguyen","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.5,"challenge":0.2,"urgency":0.4}
{"id":"mem-0029","text":"Nice — Dave would love a grilling gift. A few ideas: 1) Thermapen ONE instant-read thermometer (~$100, top-rated for smoking), 2) Weber smoker box for his gas grill (~$20, great if he doesn't already have one), 3) A set of specialty wood chips — cherry, pecan, and mesquite variety pack (~$25). The Thermapen is the gold standard if you want to go premium. Want me to check availability at the Frisco Target or order from Amazon?","title":"Gift Ideas for Dave","synapticTags":["shopping","birthday-gift","bbq","neighbors","nguyen-family"],"valence":20,"importance":0.5,"arousal":20,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-04-midday","timestampMs":1749056430000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Dave Nguyen","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Frisco","type":"LOCATION"}],"memoryType":"SEMANTIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.5,"challenge":0.1,"urgency":0.3}
{"id":"mem-0030","text":"Go with the Thermapen — order from Amazon so it gets here by Friday. Dave's going to love it. Also add a card to the order if they have funny BBQ ones.","title":"Dave Birthday Gift Order","synapticTags":["shopping","birthday-gift","amazon","neighbors"],"valence":20,"importance":0.4,"arousal":20,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-04-midday","timestampMs":1749056700000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Dave Nguyen","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.4,"challenge":0.0,"urgency":0.3}
{"id":"mem-0031","text":"Sprint retro was interesting today. The engineering team flagged that the CareConnect notification system is hitting rate limits with the third-party SMS provider. We're getting 429 errors during peak hours. Need to talk to Greg about either upgrading our Twilio tier or implementing a queue-based approach. Added it to tomorrow's stakeholder agenda.","title":"CareConnect SMS Rate Limits","synapticTags":["careconnect","work","sprint-planning","engineering","greg-conflict"],"valence":-15,"importance":1.6,"arousal":65,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-04-afternoon","timestampMs":1749063600000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"CareConnect","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Greg Holloway","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Vertex Health","type":"ORGANIZATION"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.8,"challenge":0.6,"urgency":0.7}
{"id":"mem-0032","text":"Ethan came home from piano really excited — Mrs. Patterson said he's ready to start learning Für Elise next week. He's been playing for about 8 months now and his progress is amazing. He sat down after dinner and tried to figure out the opening notes by ear. Lily danced around the living room while he played which was adorable.","title":"Ethan Piano Progress","synapticTags":["piano","ethan-growth","parenting","lily-milestone"],"valence":70,"importance":1.0,"arousal":65,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-04-evening","timestampMs":1749078000000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Ethan Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Mrs. Patterson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Lily Thompson","type":"PERSON"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.8,"challenge":0.1,"urgency":0.0}
{"id":"mem-0033","text":"Jarvis, quick journal. Busy but productive Wednesday. The 1:1 with Anika went great — I'm going to let her own the patient onboarding prioritization. Worried about Sarah though — Patricia's knee MRI has her spooked. Need to be extra supportive. Sprint retro surfaced the SMS rate limit issue which could be a problem for CareConnect launch. Ethan's piano progress is a bright spot — Für Elise next week! Also ordered Dave's birthday present. Ready for the long Thursday tomorrow with the stakeholder review.","title":"Wednesday Journal","synapticTags":["evening-journal","reflection","mentoring","patricia","careconnect","piano"],"valence":15,"importance":0.7,"arousal":20,"sessionId":"session-2026-06-04-evening","timestampMs":1749085200000,"entityMentions":[{"name":"Jarvis","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Anika Patel","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Sarah Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Patricia Morales","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"CareConnect","type":"SOFTWARE"},{"name":"Ethan Thompson","type":"PERSON"},{"name":"Dave Nguyen","type":"PERSON"}],"memoryType":"EPISODIC","recallCount":0,"interest":0.3,"challenge":0.1,"urgency":0.0}
